Sagar Ganesh Suryawanshi (1) Featured



Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Java, J2EE, RESTFUL Web Service, JPA, MySQL, Hibernate, Spring



Current Location: Pune Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune, Delhi / NCR Highest Degree: MCA

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Alpplication Programming, Application Maintenance, Java, J2EE, JavaScript, HTML, RESTFUL Web Service, JPA, MySQL, Hibernate, Spring, Spring Data JPA

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

An experienced team player with excellent communication and interpersonal skills who has the ability to work independently under pressure.

Since FEB-2014, have 5+ years of hands on experience of Java Software Development.

Working as Software Developer in Intelligic Software having 1.4 years of experience.

Having 2.7 years' experience as Software Developer at Marketplace Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Mumbai.

Having 1.8 years' experience as Software Engineer/Java Developer at SoftTantra IT Services & Consultancy Services LLP,

Having six months internship experience in Java software development at Blue Planet Info Solution Pvt. Ltd. Pune.

Work Experience

Intelligic Software Pvt. Ltd. as Software Engineer

Oct 2018 to Apr 2020

Responsibilities include provide technical solutions to the requirements. Writing Controller, services and DAO Layer Java Classes in Spring Boot. Developing the DAO?s for accessing the Database. Implementation of DAO classes for interaction with database within Business Service Layer.

Marketplace Technologies Pvt. Ltd. as Software Engineer

Mar 2016 to Oct 2018

Responsibilities include Handling Server Deployment, direct client communication and software development.

SoftTantra IT Services & Consultancy Services LLP as Software Engineer / Java Developer Feb 2014 to Oct 2015

Responsibilities include team management, direct client communication and software development.

Education

UG: B.Sc (computer application) from Amravati University in 2010

PG: MCA (Computers) from Amravati University in 2013

PG: MCA in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JAVA, J2EE			
JavaScript, HTML			
Restful Web Service			
JPA			
MySQL			
Hibernate, Spring 5			
Apache Tomcat			
Eclipse, Spring Tool Suite			
MAVEN			
Postman, GitHub			
Windows 7, Windows XP			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time